<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Articles on Oliver Weissbarth</title><link>https://oweissbarth.github.io/articles/</link><description>Recent content in Articles on Oliver Weissbarth</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 11:22:34 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://oweissbarth.github.io/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Photo or Computer graphics: The survey evaluation</title><link>https://oweissbarth.github.io/photo-or-computer-graphics-the-survey-evaluation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 21:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://oweissbarth.github.io/photo-or-computer-graphics-the-survey-evaluation/</guid><description>In the past decade computer graphics have reached a level of realism that makes it hard to distinguish them from actual photos. That is obviously pretty cool. The technological advancements have enabled artists to create amazing artwork and realize their creative vision.</description></item><item><title>Running SparkMLib with native LAPACK and BLAS</title><link>https://oweissbarth.github.io/running-sparkmlib-with-native-lapack-and-blas/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 10:37:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://oweissbarth.github.io/running-sparkmlib-with-native-lapack-and-blas/</guid><description>When getting started with the Spark maschine learning library MLib you probably saw this warning in your console: WARN BLAS: Failed to load implementation from: com.github.fommil.netlib.NativeSystemBLAS WARN BLAS: Failed to load implementation from: com.github.fommil.netlib.NativeRefBLAS WARN LAPACK: Failed to load implementation from: com.</description></item><item><title>Build php5.5 with fpm on ubuntu linux</title><link>https://oweissbarth.github.io/building-php-fpm-v5-5-ubuntu-linux/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 15:45:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://oweissbarth.github.io/building-php-fpm-v5-5-ubuntu-linux/</guid><description>In this article I’m gonna give a quick guide on building and installing php5.5 with FastCGI Process Manager on Linux. I did test it on Ubuntu 12.04 but it should work on nearly any Linux distribution out there.
 Get the source-code</description></item><item><title>Impressions from Blender Conference 2012</title><link>https://oweissbarth.github.io/articles/2012-10-17-impressions-blender-conference-2012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 18:43:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://oweissbarth.github.io/articles/2012-10-17-impressions-blender-conference-2012/</guid><description>This year I had the possbility to go to Blender Conference 2012 which is annual meetup of blenderusers and devolpers in Amsterdam.
When I arrived in Amsterdam on friday moring I was very curios about what it would be like. After seeing all the people at this year’s location “DeBalie” I knew that this was going to be amazing.</description></item><item><title>Installation of Gimp 2.8 on Ubuntu 12.04 LTS</title><link>https://oweissbarth.github.io/articles/2012-05-09-gimp-2-8-stable-installation-guide-for-ubuntu-12-04-lts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 13:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://oweissbarth.github.io/articles/2012-05-09-gimp-2-8-stable-installation-guide-for-ubuntu-12-04-lts/</guid><description>Hi guys,
Gimp 2.8 stable was officially released. To install it on a Ubuntu 12.04 you will need to install the same packages as for the RC.
If you already used the release canidate of 2.8 installing will be as easy as downloading the source from ftp://ftp.</description></item><item><title>Installing Gimp 2.7.5 on a Ubuntu 12.04 maschine</title><link>https://oweissbarth.github.io/articles/2012-03-30-installing-gimp-2-7-5-on-a-ubuntu-12-04-maschine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 17:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://oweissbarth.github.io/articles/2012-03-30-installing-gimp-2-7-5-on-a-ubuntu-12-04-maschine/</guid><description>Some days ago i read about the one-window-mode in the recent Gimp development version. So i spent some time figuring out how to get Gimp 2.7.5 running on my Ubuntu 12.04. After downloading the source code from gimp.org and running the configure-script i realized that this would be more time consuming than i thought.</description></item></channel></rss>